Guide to the New Almaden Mine (Calif.) Collection, 1845-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VII: MAPS AND PLANS
  - SURFACE FEATURE MAPS
    - Arroyo and Alamitos road to Almaden Way, old #A78, 1969; 11x17 100 (Folder 72-11)
      Santa Clara County Assessors
    - Map of block B Almaden manor with Alamitos road, 1963; 12x19 100 (Folder 72-12)
    - Portion of Capitancillos and adjacent property, Guadalupe line survey, color, 2 copies, 1962; 24x36 200 (Folder 72-13)
      R.W. Fisher
    - Alamden roadway construction sheet, sheet 5 of 8, 1966; 24x36 30 (Folder 72-14)
      Santa Clara County, C. Silcott
    - Right of way, Almaden road, 1966; 24x36 40 (Folder 72-15)
  - LOCAL/AREA MAPS
    - Map of the region adjacent to the bay of San Francisco, 1873; 24x36 2mi (Folder 73-1)
      J.D. Whitney, Hoffman
    - Map section of San Jose, Almaden, old #336, 10.5x15 (Folder 73-2)
    - Plat, land located for Z Jones, Josiah Belden, photocopy, 10.5x17 (Folder 73-3)
    - Plat of the property of the Quicksilver Mining Company, from Gunst Z239 T14 J67, 2 pieces, 8.5x11 30ch (Folder 73-4)
    - San Jose area, South Bay, Northern California, 2 copies, 16x17 (Folder 73-5)
    - Thomas Brothers map of San Jose, Santa Clara and vicinity, 16x17 (Folder 73-6)
  - PLATS
    - Plat of the part of the Rancho de los Capitancillos, 1841; 13.5 x 18.75 20ch (Folder 3-11)
      G.H. Thompson
    - Exhibit Douglada annexed to deposition of Doming Douglada 132, United States District Court, United States vs. Charles Fossat, 1861; 19 x 24.25 (Folder 3-12)
    - Exhibit J.T.S. #3 to deposition of J.T. Stratton, 1861; 19 x 24.25 (Folder 3-13)
    - Exibit J.T.S. annexed to deposition of William J. Lewis, parrott, 1861; 19 x 24.25 (Folder 3-14)
    - Map of the Rancho de los Capitancillos, exhibit, 1861; 24.25x33 20ch. (Folder 3-15)
      La Croze
    - Plat of the part of the Rancho de los Capitancillos finally confirmed to Charles Fossat, 1861; 23.25x 31.75 20ch. (Folder 4-1)
      John O. Hays
    - Plat of the part of the Rancho de los Capitancillos finally confirmed to Charles Fossat, 1861; 19 x 24.25 20ch. (Folder 4-2)
      J.C. Whitcher
    - Plat of the Rancho San Vicente, 1861; 19 x 24.25 20ch. (Folder 4-3)
      J.T. Stratton
    - Plat of the Rancho de los Capitancillos, matted, 1860; 14.75x 20 20ch. (Folder 4-4)
      John C. Hays
    - Plat of the Rancho Canada de los Capitancillos, 1871; 14x18.5 20ch. (Folder 4-5)
    - Plat of the Rancho Canada de los Capitancillos, photocopy, 1871; 14x18.5 20ch. (Folder 4-6)
    - Map of the Rancho de los Capitancillos, old #251, 20ch (Folder 4-7)
    - Pueblo and Rancho grants, 12.5x24 (Folder 4-8)
  - TUNNEL PLANS
    - Photograph of tunnel plan, mounted, old #233, 17x18.5 (Folder 73-7)
    - Unidentified, 1882; 10.5x16 (Folder 73-8)
      C.T.H.
    - Unidentified, 10.5x16 (Folder 73-9)
    - Unidentified, 1882; 10.5x16 (Folder 73-10)
    - Unidentified, 1300 level, 10.5x16 (Folder 73-11)
    - Unidentified, 1300 level, 12.25 x 24 (Folder 73-12)
    - Faull tunnel, Deep Gulch tunnel, Cora Blanca shaft, 10x11 (Folder 73-13)
    - New Ardilla shaft, Junction shaft, 18x24 (Folder 73-14)
    - Theatre, Bush tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 73-15)
    - Rattle snake drift, 18x24 (Folder 74-1)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 45x57 (Folder 74-2)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-3)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-4)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-5)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-6)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-7)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-8)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-9)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-10)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-11)
    - Unidentified, matted, color, 18x24 (Folder 74-12)
    - Cristobal tunnel, San Cristbal, 18x24 (Folder 74-13)
    - Main tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 74-14)
    - Unidentified, 17.5x19 (Folder 74-15)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-1)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-2)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-3)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-4)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-5)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-6)
    - Unidentified, 18x24 (Folder 75-7)
    - Vertical section along the center line of the new tunnel, old #182, 1858; 18x46 60 (Folder 75-8)
    - Unidentified, 27x29 (Folder 75-9)
    - Unidentified, 14x25 (Folder 75-10)
    - Labore 10, 14x25 (Folder 75-11)
    - Unidentified, 14x25 (Folder 75-12)
    - Unidentified, 14x25 (Folder 75-13)
    - Unidentified, 14x25 (Folder 75-14)
    - Unidentified, old #593, 37x48 (Folder 75-15)
    - Buena Vista incline, old #14, 24.5x35 (Folder 76-1)
    - Unidentified, fragment, 20x26 (Folder 76-2)
    - Randol crosscut, New Santa Rita West, 12x12 (Folder 76-3)
    - Randol crosscut, Juan Macios tunnel, West drift, 20x26 (Folder 76-4)
    - Pearce, Don Federico, 20x26 (Folder 76-5)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 76-6)
    - Harry tunnel, water tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 76-7)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 76-8)
    - McKinley tunnel, Cora Blanca tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 76-9)
    - Don Frederico, O'Brion, 20x26 (Folder 76-10)
    - West drift, 20x26 (Folder 76-11)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 76-12)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 76-13)
    - Buena Vista incline, 20x26 (Folder 76-14)
    - Santa Isabel shaft, 20x26 (Folder 76-15)
    - Sycamore tunnel, West Isabel tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-1)
    - Church shaft, 20x26 (Folder 77-2)
    - St. George shaft, 20x26 (Folder 77-3)
    - A. Robles tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-4)
    - Day tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-5)
    - Day tunnel incline, 20x26 (Folder 77-6)
    - Randol shaft, 20x26 (Folder 77-7)
    - Pearce drift, 20x26 (Folder 77-8)
    - McKinley tunnel, Cora Blanca tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-9)
    - Cora Blanca shaft, 20x26 (Folder 77-10)
    - Cora Blanca shaft, water tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-11)
    - Old works, 20x26 (Folder 77-12)
    - Amadavia tunnel, Hacienda tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-13)
    - Deep Gulch tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-14)
    - Hacienda tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 77-15)
    - Water tunnel, Buena Vista adit, Buena Vista shaft, 20x26 (Folder 78-1)
    - Santa Mariana, 20x26 (Folder 78-2)
    - Marqueta shaft, 20x26 (Folder 78-3)
    - San Cristobal, 20x26 (Folder 78-4)
    - San Cristobal tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-5)
    - Manuel Lopez tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-6)
    - San Cristobal tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-7)
    - San Ramon, 20x26 (Folder 78-8)
    - Lower America tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-9)
    - Bridge tunnel, Harry tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-10)
    - Bridge tunnel, Harry tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-11)
    - Bridge, tunnel, Harry tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-12)
    - Harry shaft, Harry tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-13)
    - Main tunnel, open cut tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-14)
    - Main tunnel, open cut tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 78-15)
    - Open Cut tunnel, Main tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-1)
    - El Castillo, Open Cut tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-2)
    - Far West, La Ventura, La Ardilla, Pruyn, 20x26 (Folder 79-3)
    - Relief drift, 20x26 (Folder 79-4)
    - Almaden shaft, 20x26 (Folder 79-5)
    - Upper America tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-6)
    - Santa Catarina works, Lower Velasco tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-7)
    - Lower Velasco tunnel, Santa Catarina, 20x26 (Folder 79-8)
    - Day tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-9)
    - Day tunnel, San Jose, 20x26 (Folder 79-10)
    - Great Santa Rita, Santa Rita West, Santa Rita East, 20x26 (Folder 79-11)
    - Great Santa Rita, 20x26 (Folder 79-12)
    - Relief drift, 20x26 (Folder 79-13)
    - Relief, 20x26 (Folder 79-14)
    - March tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 79-15)
    - March tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 80-1)
    - April tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 80-2)
    - A. Robles tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 80-3)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 80-4)
    - Unidentified, 20x26 (Folder 80-5)
    - Great Eastern tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 80-6)
    - Day tunnel, Great Eastern tunnel, Theatre, Velasco, 20x26 (Folder 80-7)
    - Velasco, San Dinas tunnel, Great Eastern, 20x26 (Folder 80-8)
    - Santa Rita West, Cornish, St. Patrick, Santa Rita East, 20x26 (Folder 80-9)
    - Cornish, A. Garcia, Juan Vega, 20x26 (Folder 80-10)
    - Santa Anna, Giant Powder, Ponce, Healey, 20x26 (Folder 80-11)
    - Santa Anna, Giant Powder, Ponce, Healey, 20x26 (Folder 80-12)
    - Victoria, Ossunar, Santa Anna, 20x26 (Folder 80-13)
    - March tunnel, Greely Drift, 20x26 (Folder 80-14)
    - Neff tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 80-15)
    - Great Eastern tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-1)
    - April tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-2)
    - Hell tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-3)
    - Day tunnel, Great Eastern tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-4)
    - Day tunnel, Great Eastern tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-5)
    - Bush tunnel, Day tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-6)
    - Rattle snake drift, Bush tunnel, 20x26 (Folder 81-7)
    - West drift, 20x26 (Folder 81-8)
    - Lower Grover tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 81-9)
    - McKinley tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 81-10)
    - Hacienda tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 81-11)
    - Note by A.D. Foote, 1876; 8.5x11 (Folder 81-12)
    - Hacienda tunnel, Rancho de los Capitancillos, Rancho San Vicente boundaries, 18x24 (Folder 81-13)
    - Hacienda tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 81-14)
    - Air shaft to furnace, old breast of 1867, 18x24 (Folder 81-15)
    - Church shaft, 12x12 (Folder 82-1)
    - Paull tunnel, Santa Clara #2, 12x12 (Folder 82-2)
    - Washington shaft, Santa Mariana, 12x12 (Folder 82-3)
    - Upper Santa Mariana, 12x12 (Folder 82-4)
    - Deep Gulch tunnel, 12x12 (Folder 82-5)
    - Line of projected bottom tunnel, 12x12 (Folder 82-6)
    - Mc Kinley tunnel, Cora Blanca tunnel, 12x12 (Folder 82-7)
    - Layout of buildings, Planilla shed, tracing, 1867; 12x12 (Folder 82-8)
    - San Francisco branch tunnel, Main tunnel, 12x12 (Folder 82-9)
    - Santa Clara drift, 12x12 (Folder 82-10)
    - Santa Clara drift, Santa Rosa drift, 12x12 (Folder 82-11)
    - Deep Gulch tunnel, 12x12 (Folder 82-12)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 82-13)
    - Harry shaft, 12x12 (Folder 82-14)
    - El Collegio, Santa Rosa Drift, Santa Clara drift, Pruyn, 12x12 (Folder 82-15)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-1)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-2)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-3)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-4)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-5)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-6)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-7)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-8)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-9)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-10)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-11)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-12)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-13)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-14)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 83-15)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-1)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-2)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-3)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-4)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-5)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-6)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-7)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-8)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-9)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-10)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-11)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-12)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-13)
    - Unidentified, 12x12 (Folder 84-14)
    - Near corner Cora Blanca, 2 pieces, 8.5x11 (Folder 84-15)
    - Tunnel plan, surrounding geology, notes about rocks, 6x8.5 (Folder 85-1)
    - Tunnel plan, graph, coordinates, 8.5x11 (Folder 85-2)
    - Tunnel plan, Harry, measurements, 8.5x11 (Folder 85-3)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, Harry 600, 8.5x11 100 (Folder 85-4)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, Harry 500, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-5)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, Harry, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-6)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, Harry 500, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-7)
    - Tunnel plan, mouth of Cora Blanca, Harry 500W, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-8)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, 2 pieces, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-9)
    - Tunnel plan, Open cut tunnel, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-10)
    - Tunnel plan, lower Open cut, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-11)
    - Tunnel plan, San Pedro Mine, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-12)
    - Tunnel plan, San Pedro Workings, 1880; 8.5x11 80 (Folder 85-13)
    - Tunnel plan, Juan Vega, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-14)
    - Tunnel plan, Juan Vega, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 85-15)
    - Tunnel plan, Santa Catarina, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-1)
    - Tunnel plan, Unidentified, 8.5x11 (Folder 86-2)
    - Tunnel plan, New Ardilla Sink, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-3)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca 800, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-4)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca 750S, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-5)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, 1941; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-6)
    - Tunnel plan, Cora Blanca, 1941; 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-7)
    - Tunnel plan, Los Angeles, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-8)
    - Tunnel plan, San Cristobal Adit, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-9)
    - Tunnel plan, San Cristobal Adit, 8.5x11 40 (Folder 86-10)
    - Vertical section through Day Tunnel, 13x15 20 (Folder 86-11)
    - Vertical projection, ca.1890; 9x9.5 40 (Folder 86-12)
    - Fragment, photograph of tunnel plan, Santa Isabel shaft, 4.75 x 7.25 (Folder 86-13)
    - 2100 level-2300 level, ca.1886; 14x21.5 (Folder 86-14)
    - 600 level, 18x24 (Folder 86-15)
    - Pruyn, 18x24 (Folder 87-1)
    - Tunnel plan, ca.1885; 18x24 (Folder 87-2)
    - Santa Isabel, Drain tunnel, 18x24 (Folder 87-3)
    - Working map of the San Francisco Mine, 1877; 18x24 20 (Folder 87-4)
    - Tagboard with photos pasted on, America shaft, Buena Vista on verso, 22x28 (Folder 87-5)
    - 1100-1050, 18x24 (Folder 87-6)
    - Plat of road to Margarita Mine, old #A7 & #329, 1867; 17x30 200ch (Folder 87-7)
      William Isaac
    - Map of township #9, south range No. 1 East of Mount Diablo, old #338 & #A15, 1871; 18.5 x 26.5 (Folder 87-8)
      Hardenburgh
    - Map of a road leading from the southern line of the San Vicente rancho to the Hacienda of New Almaden, old #330 & #A6, 1867; 13.5x29 2 ch (Folder 87-9)
      A.T. Hermann
    - Mineral products of the United States, ca. 1899; 24x31 (Folder 87-10)
    - Enriquita, contour, topographical, old #289, 24x30 (Folder 87-11)
    - Harry shaft workings, 1939; 34x44 50 (Folder 87-12)
    - Unidentified maps (Folder 88-1to18)
    - Damaged, fragile maps (Folder 89-1to15)
    - Damaged, fragile maps (Folder 90-1to15)
    - Damaged, fragile maps (Folder 91-1to15)
    - Damaged, fragile maps (Folder 92-1to10)
    - Topographical map, 1888 (Folder 95)
  - ROLLED MAPS
    - Plant, old #670, 42.5x70 (Folder 1)
    - Triangulations for topographical map, surroundings of Enriquita, old #270, 1883; 44x59 200 (Folder 2)
      Read
    - Cora Blanca Mine, old #76, 1876; 39.5x55 20 (Folder 3)
    - Working map of the San Francisco mine, old #400, 1877; 45x49 20 (Folder 4)
    - Cora Blanca, San Francisco, Main Tunnel, old #220, 37.5x107 40 (Folder 5)
    - Randol shaft, old #24A, 27.5x51 (Folder 6)
    - Plan of the Randol shaft, blueprint, building layout, old #570, 1916; 27x50.5 50 (Folder 7)
      B.O. Webber
    - Profile of the New Almaden Mines, blueprint, old #263, 11.5 x 136.5 200, 100 (Folder 8)
    - Principal workings on the vertical plane of the Main Tunnel of the New Almaden Mine, section #1, old #185, 1864; 18.75 x 55 60 (Folder 9)
    - San Jose and Almaden railroad crossing of SPRR, 2 copies, old #626, 1912; 18x61 200 (Folder 10)
    - Direct acting hoisting gear and direct acting pumping gear, old #612, 26.5x48 2 (Folder 11)
    - Section #2, showing the principal working on the vertical plane of the new tunnel of the New Almaden Mine, old #191, 1864; 19x63 60 (Folder 12)
    - Area geography, New Almaden Mine, old #320B, 1935; 22 x 68.75 400 (Folder 13)
    - Branch line #1, San Jose and Almaden railroad crossings of Southern Pacific railroad, old #629, 1912; 30.5x48 200 (Folder 14)
    - Pit work for Buena Vista shaft, old #632, 1882; 30 x 118.5 4 (Folder 15)
    - Tunnel plan, Day tunnel workings, old #216, 25x94.5 40 (Folder 16)
    - Tentative subdivision map, Almaden Villa, 1960; 31x50 (Folder 17)
      Ruth and Going
    - New Almaden Property surface map, old #293, 1935; x71 400 (Folder 18)
    - New Almaden Property surface map, old #293, 1935; x71 400 (Folder 19)
    - Enriquita Mine, and surrounding area, old #260, 27x48 60 (Folder 20)
    - Santa Mariana, old #470, 1874; 28x48 20 (Folder 21)
    - La Providencia, old #525, 1874; 29x47 20 (Folder 22)
    - Tunnel plan, old #113, 34x43 (Folder 23)
    - Coordinates, 44x53 (Folder 24)
    - Rancho San Vicente, old #253, 1926; 35x38.5 10 ch (Folder 25)
      California Pacific Titl and Trust Co.
    - Sketch showing general vertical sections of the Quicksilver Mining Company principal mines, 1876; 51x217 (Folder 26)
    - Tunnel plans, Deep Gulch tunnel, Harry tunnel, Santa Rosa drift, 33x41.4 100 (Folder 27)
    - Tunnel plans, Grey shaft, Deep Gluch tunnel, Cora Blanca shaft, 33x143 (Folder 28)
    - Tunnel plans, Randol shaft, New Santa Rita West, 42x65 (Folder 29)
    - Tunnel plans, Santa Rita, Great Santa Rita, Santa Rita West, Santa Rita East, old #181, 38x111 (Folder 30)
    - Randol shaft, 900 level, 38x48 40 (Folder 31)
    - New Almaden property, from J.H. Farrel's report of October 1923, 2 copies, 36.5x 50 (Folder 32)
    - Surface feature map, with landmarks, old #312, 37x69 (Folder 33)
    - Buena Vista, Santa Isabel, 2000-2100 levels, 39x67 40 (Folder 34)
    - Surface feature map, with landmarks, old #267, 38x69 (Folder 35)
    - General vertical section of principle mines, old #222, 1878; 47.5x365 (Folder 36)
    - Day tunnel, Randol shaft, St. George shaft, 38.5x67 40 (Folder 37)
    - Surface feature map, updated by Jimmie Schneider, 1967, 1935; 33x78 (Folder 38)
      C.N. Schuette F. Frederick
    - Map showing the workings in the principal mines, 1876; 104x157 20 (Folder 39)
    - Surface feature map, with landmarks, 37x69 (Folder 40)
    - Washington shaft, Santa Rita shaft, Randol shaft, 41x94 40 (Folder 41)
    - Pueblo lands, tract #3, Rancho de los Capitancillos, Rancho San Vicente, boundary coordinates, 1926; 43x61 10ch. (Folder 42)
    - Guadalupe, surface feature map, tunnel plans reverse print, 42x55 20 (Folder 43)
    - Plan of the New Almaden Mine, old #190, 1856-1864; 34x54 60 (Folder 44)
    - Tunnel plan, Randol shaft, 1200, 1300, and 1400 levels, 39x70 40 (Folder 45)
    - Survey of portion of the Day tunnel, old #212, 1942; 44x87 40 (Folder 46)
      Thornburgh
    - Surface feature map, updated by Jimmie Schneider, 1967, 1935; 33x78 (Folder 47)
    - New Almaden, San Francisco and Cora Blanca mines on Quicksilver Mining Company land, old #221, 1876; 41x162 40 (Folder 48)
    - Tunnel plans, Randol shaft, 37x116 (Folder 49)
    - Tunnel plans, America, Harry, Almaden, and Santa Alta shafts, 37x148 (Folder 50)
    - Guadalupe, surface feature map, tunnel plans, 2 copies, 42x55 20 (Folder 51)
    - Blueprint of large rolled map, section #1, 36x95 (Folder 52)
    - Blueprint of large rolled map, section #2, 36x45 (Folder 53)
    - Blueprint of large rolled map, section #3, 36x117 (Folder 54)
    - Blueprint of large rolled map, section #4, 36x149 (Folder 55)
    - Guadalupe Dam, aerial photograph, 27.5x28 (Folder 56)
    - Almaden Dam, aerial photograph, 26x44 (Folder 57)
    - Panorama photograph, 19x40 (Folder 58)
    - Neyland, Portola Valley, aerial photograph, 27x28 (Folder 59)
    - Aerial photograph, 27x28 (Folder 60)
    - New Almaden, Cora Blanca, San Francisco Mines, 1882; 42x169 40 (Folder 61)
      E.N. Eager
    - La Cora Blanca, old #73 & B32, ca.1875; 37x53 20 (Folder 62)
      C.T. Healey
    - Mine Hill progress map, Stadia survey, Engineering office copy, old #151, 34x44 40 (Folder 63)
    - Mine Hill progress map, tracing, 29x36 (Folder 64)
    - Randol shaft, 1800 level, 37x39 40 (Folder 65)
    - Almaden Mine, 700 level, old #214, 1942; 36x47 40 (Folder 66)
    - Contour map, old #259, 37x59 200 (Folder 67)
    - Tunnel plan, Almaden shaft, old #450, 33x36.5 (Folder 68)
    - Tunnel plan, San Francisco shaft, old #442E, 35x46 (Folder 69)
    - Tunnel plan, Santa Isabel shaft, 37x38.5 (Folder 70)
    - Composite map of Harry workings, 1944; 36x44 50 (Folder 71)
    - Composite map of Harry workings, 1944; 36x44 50 (Folder 72)
    - Composite map of Harry workings, old #95F, 1944; 36x46 50 (Folder 73)
    - Plan of the Senator Mine, old #572, 1919; 35x46 50 (Folder 74)
    - New Almaden Mine, 700 level, Old #213, 33x34 (Folder 75)
    - Plan of the Senator Mine, reverse negative, 1919; 35x46 50 (Folder 76)
    - Mine Hill progress map, old #152N, 34x43 40 (Folder 77)
    - Mine Hill benches, old #152B, 1944; 34x43 40 (Folder 78)
    - Mine Hill benches, old #152C, 1944; 34x43 40 (Folder 79)
    - Mine Hill benches, old #152D, 1944; 34x43 40 (Folder 80)
    - Mine Hill benches, old #152E, 1944; 34x43 40 (Folder 81)
    - Mine Hill progress map, old #150A, 1941; 33x44 40 (Folder 82)
    - Mine Hill progress map, office copy, old #150B, 1941; 33x44 40 (Folder 83)
    - Mine Hill progress map, engineering office copy, old #150C, 1941; 33x44 40 (Folder 84)
    - Mine Hill progress map, engineering office copy, old #150D, 1941; 33x44 40 (Folder 85)
    - Mine Hill progress map, engineering office copy, old #150E, 1941; 33x44 40 (Folder 86)
    - Tunnel plan, 36x42 (Folder 87)
    - Tunnel plans, Santa Rita shaft area, 37x43 (Folder 88)
    - Tentative subdivision map, Almaden Villa, 1960; 31x49 (Folder 89)
    - New Almaden Mine, 600 level, old #189, 1942; 35x48 40 (Folder 90)
    - Plan of the Senator Mine, old #572, 1919; 35x46 50 (Folder 91)
    - Harry shaft workings, old #74, 1935; 34x43.5 40 (Folder 92)
    - Composite map, Harry workings, old #A29, 1944; 32x37 50 (Folder 93)
      United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey
    - Pueblos land, tract #3, Rancho de los Capitancillos, Rancho San Vicente, boundary coordinates, 36x39.5 (Folder 94)
    - Pueblos land, tract #3, Rancho de los Capitancillos, Rancho San Vicente, boundary coordinates, 36x39.5 (Folder 95)
    - Pueblos land, reverse print, old #A28, 35x40 (Folder 96)
    - Tunnel plans, Main tunnel, San Pablo shaft, 34x36 (Folder 97)
    - Tunnel plans, Santa Rita shaft, March raise, 800 level Day tunnel, 38x42 40 (Folder 98)
    - Tunnel plans, negative print, 38x42 40 (Folder 99)
    - Contour map, New Almaden, old #255, 1956; 32x45 (Folder 100)
      John T. Whitaker
    - Rotary furnace area, New Almaden Mines, 1968; 36.5x42 20 (Folder 101)
      J. Atwood, J.O. Challend
    - Tunnel plan, Junction shaft, Santa Rita, Great Eastern, 36.5x49 (Folder 102)
    - Contour map, with wooden end pieces, old #264, 46x60 (Folder 103)
    - Randol shaft, Buena Vista, old #31, 1887; 52x85 20 (Folder 104)
    - Working map for the lower levels of New Almaden, old #32, 1876; 48x92 20 (Folder 105)
    - Vertical section of the bottom tunnel, Cora Blanca Mine, old #84, ca.1974; 25x89 (Folder 106)
    - Tunnel plans, America shaft, 43x75 (Folder 107)
    - Buena Vista shaft, Santa Isabel, old #1, 43.5x54 (Folder 108)
    - Contours, geology, 53.5x65 (Folder 109)
    - Enriquita Mine, old #526, 30x86.5 10 (Folder 110)
    - Contours, old #258, 34x49 (Folder 111)
    - Hacienda tunnel vertical section of the bottom tunnel, 1200 level, 20x78 80 (Folder 112)
    - Triangulation for topographical map, below Buena Vista shaft, old #252, 1883; 46x60 200 (Folder 113)
    - Surface features, contours, old #257, 36x37 (Folder 114)
    - Randol shaft, 1000 level, 39x53 40 (Folder 115)
    - Survey of pipe line for bringing water to summit of Mine Hill, old #262, 1882; 27x97 100 (Folder 116)
    - Mine Hill Open Cut surface map, old #150, 1941; 30x40 40 (Folder 117)
    - Straight line profile from Randol Planilla to Hacienda furnaces, old #339, 16.5x66 100 (Folder 118)
    - Tunnel plan, San Francisco Mine, 36x45 40 (Folder 119)